A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, General Files FA1092
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, President, General Files
c. 1956-1978
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA1092
2.62 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes.
2 standard record storage boxes.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Box 1: Received 1981 April 29. Box 2: Received 1981 October 7.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 325-U
Arrangement
Arranged in original order as received.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, memoranda, reports and general files pertaining to national and international organizations and real estate matters.
- National and International Organizations, 1
  - American Council on Education, 1956-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Council on Education, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Committion on the Future of Higher Education (Clark Kerr), 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1962-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of New York State, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Council for the International Exchange of Scholars, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) Guide for Grants and Contracts, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) Guide for Grants and Contracts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) Guide for Grants and Contracts, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Itnernational Education, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Universities, 1963-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - International Union for the Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fulbright-Hays Program (Committee on International Exchange of Persons), 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Health Research Council, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - HEW - General, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - HEW - Office of Education, 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - HEW - General re: Grants, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - HEW - NIH/PHS, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - HEW - NIH Guide II, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - National Academy of Science - General, 1969-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - National Academy of Science - Printed Materials (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - National Academy of Science - Presidential Prizes for Innovation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - National Academy of Science - Chinese Scientists' Visit, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - National Academy of Science - USSR Scientists' Visits, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - National Education Association, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities "News", 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - National Research Council, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - National Academy of Sciences Council, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - National Science Foundation/Rockefeller University: Interdisciplinary Lab. Program (ARPA) Evaluation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - National Society for Medical Research, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Real Estate Files, ca. 1969-1978; 2
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Proposals made to RU: Kaye, Langer (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Proposals made to RU: General, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Proposals made to RU: Medical Tower 500 East 62nd Street (Keith Black), 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - RU Real Estate: General, 1969-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Housing: General, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Working File: Sacony and the City Block, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8, Folder 9)
  - Ms. Roni Diamond: City Block (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Socony Apartments, 1969-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Operation Statements, Socony City Block, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12, Folder 13)
  - Sale of Sutton Terrace (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "The City Block", 1969-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16, Folder 15)
  - Sutton Terrace: General, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17, Folder 18)
  - Sutton Terrace: Insurance papers, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sutton Terrace: Financial matters, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20, Folder 21)
  - Sutton House, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Renovations (Rockefeller University), 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Renovations: McGinnity report, 1973 March 19 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Property Managements III (East River Management), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Operation Statements, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)